socialraves.com 2016-04-15

# Privacy Policy | Social Raves

**This privacy policy was last modified on: May 1, 2010.**

This privacy policy sets forth and explains how personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by Zengo Networks, Inc. with respect to your use of the Social Raves website (“Site”) located at http://www.socialraves.com to help you make an informed decision about using the Site.  
****

**Definition of Personal Information**

The term “personal information” means information that specifically identifies an individual (e.g., name, address, telephone number, email), as well as information about that individual’s location or activities (e.g., information about his or her use of the Site) when directly linked to personally identifiable information. A user name may be personal information if it includes personally identifying information such as a first and last name. Personal information also includes demographic information (e.g., date of birth, gender, geographic location) when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies the individual person. Personal information excludes aggregated data which is data collected about usage of the Site or about a group or category of products, services or users, in which individual identities or personally identifiable information have been removed. How individuals use the Site and its associated services may be collected and combined with information about how other users use the Site and such services. Aggregated data allows us understand overall trends and statistics about usage of the Site so that we can better tailor and improve users’ experiences. As such, this privacy policy does not restrict or limit our collection and use of aggregated information.  
****

**Information We Collect**

When registering on our Site, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, and zip code. Any data that we request that is not required will be clearly specified as voluntary or optional. We also collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, fill out a form, respond to a survey, build a profile, write a review, post an event, start a discussion or conversation, leave comments, upload content including photos and videos, send an email or private message to another user, interact with other users, or participate in any of the social features and functionality of the Site. Some information – such as your IP address, operating system, the browser type, the address of a referring web site, and your activity on the Site – is automatically collected. These data are considered and will be treated as personal information only when linked to any of the personally identifiable information mentioned above. We may also collect from time to time other demographic and contact information to enable your participation in contests, games, promotions, and the like that we may run on the Site from time to time.

**Use of Cookies and Clear GIFs**

Like most websites, we use cookies to enhance the user experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to the Site. Cookies are small files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your browser (if you allow) that enables us to recognize your browser and capture, as well as remember, certain information. Clear GIFs are small, invisible graphic images that we may use on the Site or in emails we send about the Site to collect certain information and monitor user activity on the Site. Cookies and clear GIFs are considered personal information only when linked to any of the personally identifiable information mentioned above.

Ads on the Site may be served to users through arrangements we have with various third parties. These third parties may place their own cookies, clear GIFs or other devices on your computer to collect non-personal information which may be used, among other things, to deliver ad messages targeted to your interests, as well as better understand the usage and visitation of our Site. This privacy policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for, cookies, clear GIFs, and other devices that may be in third party ads served on our Site. You are therefore advised to check the privacy policies of advertisers and/or ad services to learn about their use of cookies and other technology. Moreover, you can manage the handling of cookies with your browser so you can be warned about cookies, automatically block them, or delete them. Note, however, that if you set your browser to not accept or reject cookies, some portions or sections of the Site may not work properly or as it was designed.

**How We Use Your Information  
**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in any one of the following ways: to personalize your experience; to offer products and services that may be of interest to you; to improve the website and service based on the information and feedback we receive from you; to improve customer service by more effectively responding to service requests and needs; manage your account and your preferences; send emails based on activity directly connected with your account; announce service changes, product enhancements, and the like; as well as enforce the Terms of Service of the Site.

Personal information you provide may be aggregated and combined with other users’ data so we can better understand your needs and continually evolve the service to ensure that these needs are met. We may also use aggregated information for the purpose of informing users about our products and/or services as well as those of our partners or third parties. In the event that we obtain information from such partners or third parties, we may append that information with other data that we already have and maintain about you.  
****

**How We Protect Your Information**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit a request or access your personal information. These security measures include password-protected directories and databases to safeguard your information, SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) technology to ensure that your information is fully encrypted and sent across the Internet securely, and PCI Scanning to actively protect our servers from hackers and other vulnerabilities.  
****

**Disclosure to Outside Parties**

We will never sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website and conducting our business, so long as those third parties agree to keep this information confidential. We are, however, not responsible for the actions of these third parties, nor for any additional information that you provide directly to them. You are therefore advised and encouraged to understand the practices of such third parties with regards to privacy before choosing to disclose any of your personal information to them.

We may also release your information when we believe disclosing it is appropriate in terms of compliance with the law, enforce the Site’s policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, and other uses. Nothing in this privacy policy restricts the sharing of aggregated data which may be shared with third parties without your consent.

Please recognize that any information you post in your profile and in any of the interactive sections of the Site are available for other users to see and, in some cases, may be viewable publicly.  
****

**Links to Third Party Websites**

We may include or offer links to third party websites on our Site. These third party sites have separate privacy policies that are independent from ours. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these third party sites.  
****

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your prior consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make may changes to their information at any time by logging into their account and editing their profile. In addition, we do not collect any information from anyone under the age of 13. Our website and its service is directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.  
****

**Online Privacy Only**

This privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Site and not to information collected offline.  
****

**Your Consent**

By using the Site, you consent to our privacy policy.  
****

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and update the privacy modification date above. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. You are encouraged to revisit this page from time to time to make sure you are up to date and understand how personal information you provide may be used.  
****

**Questions About the Privacy Policy**

If you have any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact us by sending an email with your inquiry at [privacy@socialraves.com](mailto:privacy@socialraves.com).
